Donatello: COUNTLESS MILES OF CYBERSPACE COMBED OVER.
INNUMEROUS LINES OF PROGRAMMING CODE SCOURED.
A MYRIAD OF BYTES, NODES, AND CACHES SCRUTINIZED.
BUT FINALLY, 92,643 NANOSCOPIC DATA BITS LATER,
OUR FATHER IS ABOUT TO BE WHOLE AGAIN.
UH, THAT'S ASSUMING THIS WORKS.
IT HAS TO WORK.
I DESIGNED THE CYBERMAT PORTAL TO CONVERT MATTER INTO CODE,
SO BY REVERSING THE POLARITY OF THE DEFAULT STASIS APPLICATION,
CODE SHOULD BE ABLE TO BE CONVERTED BACK INTO MATTER.
SOUNDS LIKE YOU'VE GOT EVERYTHING COVERED, DONNIE.
YEAH. ESPECIALLY THE BIG WORDS.
WELL, HERE GOES.
FATHER! FATHER!FATHER!
ALL RIGHT! YEAH!
WE WERE SO WORRIED.
HOW MANY FINGERS AM I HOLDING UP?
ARE YOU OKAY? HOW YOU FEELING?
I FEEL...
WHOLE...
AND HAPPY TO BE HOME...
THOUGH A BIT LIGHT-HEADED.
THE MATTER CONVERSION PROCESS IS STRESSFUL, FATHER.
LET'S GET YOU SOME REST.
Serling: REST?
HE NEEDS TO PACK.
WE'RE SCHEDULED TO DEPART FOR THE WEDDING IN MINUTES.
OH. AND WELCOME BACK, SIR.
UH, WEDDING?
YEAH, CASEY AND APRIL'S.
ABOUT TIME, RIGHT?
MY SONS, LET US CELEBRATE OUR REUNION.
AND I CAN THINK OF NO BETTER PLACE TO DO SO
THAN THE UNION OF CASEY AND APRIL.
FATHER, IF YOU'RE UP FOR IT, SO AM I.
LET'S FINALLY PUT THE PROBLEMS OF CYBERSPACE BEHIND US.
IT'S NINJA TIME!
♪ IN THE CITY, ON THE SCENE, UNDERGROUND, OR IN BETWEEN ♪
♪ THERE'S A MEAN, GREEN TEAM OF HEROES LIKE YOU'VE NEVER SEEN ♪
♪ AND WHEN THE VILLAINS AND TURTLES FIGHT ♪
♪ IT'S GONNA BE ONE SHELL OF A SIGHT ♪
♪ YOU KNOW THE TURTLES GOT YOUR ♪
♪ BACK, BACK TO THE SEWER
♪ TEENAGE MUTANT NINJA TURTLES
ROLL CALL!
♪ LEONARDO, DONATELLO
♪ RAFAEL, MICHELANGELO
♪ I LOVE BEING A TURTLE
♪ THERE'S A MEAN, GREEN TEAM OF HEROES LIKE YOU'VE NEVER SEEN ♪
♪ DOIN' EVERYTHING THEY CAN
♪ TO STOP EVIL SHREDDER'S PLAN
♪ OH, YEAH, THE TURTLES ARE
♪ BACK, BACK TO THE SEWER
♪ TEENAGE MUTANT NINJA TURTLES
♪ TEENAGE MUTANT NINJA TURTLES ♪
♪ BACK TO THE SEWER
Raphael: CASEY'S GRANDMA'S FARMHOUSE, HERE WE COME!
YOU KNOW, RAPH,
SOME PEOPLE HEAD TO THE COUNTRY FOR A SLOWER PACE OF LIFE.
SORRY, BRO, BUT I AIN'T SOME PEOPLE.
I'M THE BEST MAN.
I GOT DUTIES, LIKE TEACHING CASEY HOW TO TIE A TIE...
WHICH, MAY TAKE A WHILE
SEEING AS HOW THAT AIN'T ONE OF MY BETTER NINJA SKILLS.
MAN, SERLING, I AM SO LOOKING FORWARD TO THIS.
I LOVE WEDDINGS.
WHEN HAVE YOU EVER BEEN TO A WEDDING?
BEEN TO? NEVER.
SEEN ON TV? ALL THE TIME.
EVERY SERIES EVENTUALLY DOES A WEDDING EPISODE, DUDE.
I'M NOT PICKING UP
ANY VIRTUAL FLUCTUATIONS OR DISTORTIONS, MASTER.
THE DIGITAL-TO-PHYSICAL CONVERSION
HAS BEEN A COMPLETE SUCCESS.
I AM GLAD TO HEAR IT, MY SON.
HEY, GUYS. WE'RE HERE.
THEY'RE HERE!
AND SO IS MASTER SPLINTER.
IT'S SO GOOD TO SEE YOU.
THIS MAKES OUR WEDDING EVEN MORE SPECIAL.
PERFECT, EVEN.
SENSEI, YOU LOOK LIKE A MILLION BUCKS.
HEH. BETTER THAN A MILLION PIECES, RIGHT?
COME ON IN, EVERYONE. TAKE A LOAD OFF.
I'M TELLIN' YA, THE SHREDDER NEVER STOOD A CHANCE.
YES, I HAVE HEARD.
MY SONS HAVE MADE THEIR FATHER QUITE PROUD.
HOW ABOUT YOU, MASTER SPLINTER?
WHAT WAS CYBERSPACE LIKE?
IT WAS...STRANGE.
I HAD NO SINGLE SENSE OF SELF,
BUT, RATHER, A MULTITUDE OF THOUGHTS AND FEELINGS.
Splinter: COMMON TO THEM ALL, HOWEVER,
WAS A LONGING TO RETURN TO MY FAMILY.
WELL, DONNIE SURE TOOK CARE OF THAT.
YEAH, THAT BIG OLD BRAIN OF HIS
WAS WORKING OVERTIME TO GET YOU OUT OF THERE SAFE AND SOUND.
HUH? HUH?HUH?
ARE YOU GUYS EXPECTING SOMEONE?
NO, NONE OF THE GUESTS ARE DUE TO ARRIVE UNTIL THE MORNING.
MA?
CASEY!
THAT'S ASSUMING CASEY GOT THE DATES ON THE INVITATIONS RIGHT.
WELL, UH, ALL THOSE LETTERS AND NUMBERS
SEEM THE SAME WHEN YOU'RE WRITIN' IN CALLIGRAPHY.
HEY, CUZ.
UHH!
WHAT'S SHAKING, APRIL?
WHA-- UH...
Casey's Mom: DON'T YOU WORRY, CASEY.
I TOLD YOUR COUSIN SID
IF HE TELLS A SOUL ABOUT YOUR SPECIAL FRIENDS,
I'LL BUST HIS KNEECAPS.
WHAT A LONG JOURNEY THIS HAS BEEN.
Together: ANCIENT ONE?!
GUESS I'D BETTER GO GET THE SPARE BLANKETS.
BLANKETS? WHAT A TREAT.
PROFESSOR?!PROFESSOR?!PROFESSOR?!
WHAT UP, GUYS?ANGEL?
SEE? THIS IS WHY I LOVE WEDDINGS.
I HEAR YOU.
NOTHING BEATS BEING SURROUNDED BY FRIENDS AND FAMILY.
WE HAVE THEIR POSITION,
AND SOON, IN THE NAME OF THE MASTER,
WE SHALL HAVE THEIR HEADS!
Raphael: I'M TELLING YOU -- THE RABBIT GOES IN THE HOLE,
AROUND THE TREE, AND THEN...
VOILà!
UH.
HUH?
UH, YOU SURE THIS IS RIGHT?
UH, GUYS?
THE CEREMONY STARTS IN AN HOUR.
SO, GETTING NERVOUS YET?
ME? NERVOUS?
COME ON!
I'VE TAKEN ON ENTIRE STREET GANGS SINGLE-HANDEDLY...
GONE MANO A MANO WITH SOME OF THE BIGGEST BADDIES
IN THE CRIMINAL UNDERWORLD...
FOUGHT MONSTERS, MUTANTS, AND ALIENS.
I MEAN, YOU THINK I'LL GET NERVOUS
JUST 'CAUSE TODAY I'M GETTING MAR--
MAR-- MAR--
OH.
WHOA, THERE!
NICE GOING, BEST MAN.
HEY, JUST BE GLAD NONE OF THOSE MONSTERS OR MUTANTS
EVER PROPOSED.
OKAY, APRIL.
YOUR VEIL IS ALL READY.
I ALSO PUT TOGETHER THE BOUTONNIERES
AND FLORAL ARRANGEMENTS --
ONE FOR EVERY GUEST.
THANKS, MIKEY.
YOU'RE THE BEST BRIDESMAID EVER.
BRIDESMAID?!
GIVE A TURTLE A LITTLE RESPECT.
I'M THE MAID OF HONOR. YAAAHH!
SO, HOW DO I LOOK?
AHH!
BEAUTIFUL!
RIGHT THIS WAY, LADIES AND GENTLEMEN...
AND, UH, NONE OF THE ABOVES.
INTERDIMENSIONAL...
OH, I GIVE UP.
DONATELLO.
GOOD TO SEE YOU.
WHERE IS YOUR GIFT, GEN?
GIFTS, USAGI?
WE WERE SUPPOSED TO BRING GIFTS?
WELL, I'M SURE...
HISOMI WON'T MIND IF I SHARE HIS.
I GUESS, UH, YOU'RE HISOMI.
CAPTAIN MORTU, I'M PLEASED TO REPORT
THAT THERE IS NO SUSHI BAR AT THE RECEPTION.
THANK GOODNESS.
WE WOULDN'T WANT A REPEAT OF WHAT HAPPENED LAST TIME.
I STILL SMELL LIKE SOY SAUCE.
YOU OKAY, LEATHERHEAD?
OH, YES. I'M FINE, ANGEL.
I JUST ALWAYS CRY AT WEDDINGS.
WELL, THAT'S JUST ABOUT EVERYONE.
YOU GUYS SEEN APRIL?
I HAVEN'T SEEN APRIL. SHE'S NOT HERE.
YOU THINK SHE'S HAVIN' SECOND THOUGHTS?
AW, I KNEW THIS WOULD HAPPEN.
EASY, MY SON.
IT IS TRADITION FOR THE GROOM
NOT TO SEE THE BRIDE BEFORE THE CEREMONY.
SHE IS PREPARING HERSELF IN THE FARMHOUSE.
I WILL FETCH HER.
HMM.
THE FOOT!
I MUST WARN THE OTHERS.
OH! OH.
YOU WILL WARN NO ONE, RODENT.
Man: I WONDER WHAT'S TAKING SO LONG.
April: Psst! GUYS?
EVERYTHING OKAY?
APRIL?
WHOA...BABE.
YOU LOOK BEAU-- BEA--
BEA-- UGH.
WHOA!
EASY, KILLER.
SORRY FOR THE DELAY.
MASTER SPLINTER WENT TO FIND YOU.
YOU HAVEN'T SEEN HIM?
NO.
I WONDER WHERE HE COULD --
WHOA! MASTER SPLINTER!
MASTER SPLINTER...
HE'S HERE.
HE'S --
WHAT THE SHELL'S GOING ON?
YOUR LONG-AWAITED DEMISE.
Donatello: THE SHREDDER?
ATTACK!
HA!
I DON'T REMEMBER GETTING YOUR RSVP, BUCKET-FOR-BRAINS.
YEAH. LIKE, DIDN'T WE FRY YOU UP EXTRA-CRISPY-STYLE?
MY BODY PERHAPS.
BUT THE ELECTRIC CURRENT YOU SOUGHT TO DESTROY ME WITH
DID NOT DAMAGE MY DIGITAL CORE.
DIGITAL CORE?
YES.
I ESCAPED BACK TO CYBERSPACE
WHERE I WAS ABLE TO ABSORB THE MASSIVE INFLUX OF ENERGY.
ENERGY THAT ALLOWED ME TO RECONSTITUTE MYSELF
TO BECOME MORE POWERFUL THAN EVER.
YEAH. I'M KIND OF GETTIN' THAT.
THEN IT WAS SIMPLY A MATTER
OF INFECTING ONE OF THE RAT'S DATA BITS
WITH A LINE OF CODE THAT, ONCE CONVERTED INTO MATTER,
BECAME A HOMING BEACON...
WHICH LED ME RIGHT TO YOU...
AND THIS MOST AUSPICIOUS OCCASION.
OH.
YOU CRASHED THE WRONG WEDDING, KHAN!
DONNIE, WE'LL HANDLE THE SHREDDER.
GET MASTER SPLINTER OUT OF HERE.
YOU'LL HANDLE NOTHING.
YOUR ATTEMPTS TO DESTROY ME HAVE ONLY MADE ME FASTER...
STRONGER!
AND IT WILL NOW COST YOU EVERYTHING.
IT IS TIME.
FAREWELL, WORMS.
OH, DEAR!
NO! NO!NO!NO!
AND NOW IT IS YOUR TURN TO PERISH.
WAIT. LOOK!
SOMETHING'S STILL MOVING IN THERE.
DONNIE, CHECK IT OUT.
MIKEY AND I WILL BACK UP RAPH.
YOUR BROTHER IS WISE TO RUN.
STILL, HE ONLY POSTPONES THE INEVITABLE.
I WILL DESTROY YOU ALL.
EVERYONE OUT! HURRY!
COME ON.
WE'VE GOT TO GET MASTER SPLINTER BACK TO THE HAULER.
IT'S SAFE, AND IT MIGHT JUST GIVE US OUR ONLY CHANCE
AT BEATING THE SHREDDER.
FINISH THEM.
THE SHREDDER SAID HE HAD A DIGITAL CORE.
IF WE CAN GET A SAMPLING OF THAT CORE'S CODING SIGNATURE,
WE MIGHT BE ABLE TO USE IT AGAINST HIM.
Serling: A DIGITAL CORE?
BUT I THOUGHT IN THIS WORLD,
THE SHREDDER WAS MADE ENTIRELY OF MATTER.
SO DID I.
BUT SINCE THIS SHREDDER WAS BORN OUT OF VIRAL'S BODY,
HE MUST HAVE INHERITED SOME OF HER DIGITAL PROPERTIES.
SO HOW DO WE GET THIS SAMPLING, MY SON?
WITH THIS!
THE SHREDDER INFECTED ONE OF YOUR DATA BITS
SO THAT, WHEN CONVERTED INTO MATTER, IT BECAME THIS BEACON.
IF WE COULD CONVERT IT BACK INTO CODE,
WE'LL HAVE OUR SAMPLE AND ALL THE DATA WE NEED
TO DESTROY THE SHREDDER THE SAME WAY WE DESTROYED VIRAL...
WITH YOUR DECOMPILING BLAST.
SO, WHAT DO YOU THINK THE ODDS ARE
OF US GETTIN' THROUGH THIS?
STATISTICALLY SPEAKING...
BAD.
YEAH? WELL I'D SAY THEY JUST GOT A LITTLE BIT BETTER.
LOOK!
IT'S THE JUSTICE FORCE.
SORRY WE'RE LATE.
OH, AND CONGRATULATIONS FROM ALL OF US.
AAH!
THIS IS YOUR END.
Splinter: UNHAND MY SONS.
WHAT?! HA!
WHAT COULD YOU POSSIBLY DO TO MAKE ME?
THIS!
PATHETIC.
YOU ARE POWERLESS TO DEFEAT ME.
I CAN'T GET A SHOT THROUGH THAT SHIELD.
IT'S IMPERVIOUS TO THE DECOMPILER BEAM.
BUT PERHAPS IT IS NOT IMPERVIOUS TO FLESH AND BLOOD.
GRRR!
I WILL NEVER FALL TO YOU, RAT.
IT WAS NOT MY AIM TO MAKE YOU FALL.
HUH?
NO!
NICE SHOT! WAY TO GO, DONNIE!
Casey: HEY, RAPH.
I THINK I FINALLY FIGURED OUT
HOW TO TIE THIS THING.
CASEY!
NOW, THEN, LET'S NOT LET A FEW BAD APPLES RUIN ALL THE FUN.
I BELIEVE THERE'S A WEDDING TO BE HAD.
YES.
BUT PERHAPS...OUTSIDE.
NO MATTER HOW MANY TIMES I'VE BEEN TO THIS WEDDING,
IT ALWAYS MAKES ME CRY.
AND SO, BY THE POWERS VESTED IN ME BY PLANET D'HOONNIB,
IT GIVES ME GREAT PLEASURE TO PRONOUNCE YOU, CASEY JONES,
AND YOU, APRIL O'NEIL, MAN AND WIFE.
YOU MAY KISS THE BRIDE.
YEAH! HA HA HA!
CAPTIONS PAID FOR BY 4KIDS PRODUCTIONS, INC.