- ♪
- Huh?
- [cat screeching]
- [garbage can rattling]
- Blasted cat!
- ♪
- Oh!
- [club clattering]
- HUN: Huh?
- RAPHAEL: Where's
Spike and Bam-Bam?
- [snarling]
Show yourself, already!
This is Purple Dragon turf
and you're gonna pay
for trespassing!
- [snarling]
Oh!
- [weapon rattling]
- HUN: Mohawk?
[snarling]
Keep your eyes open.
- ♪
- [kicks, grunts
of combat]
- Huh?
What the...?
I'm not afraid of you!
[grunting]
- Then you are a fool.
- ♪
- [gasping]
You? But...but...
that...that's impossible.
- Nothing is impossible
to me, worm.
- [weapon blasting]
- [roaring]
- [weapon piece clanks]
- HUN: [grunting]
- CYBER SHREDDER:
[grunting]
- [heavy thud]
- HUN: [groaning]
- The time has come to
remind this city
who its true master is.
[nasty laughter]
- ♪
- ♪ It's ninja time!
- ♪ In the city,
on the scene ♪
♪ Underground
and in between ♪
♪
♪ There's a mean,
green team of heroes ♪
♪ Like you've never seen
♪ And when the villains
and turtles fight ♪
- Let's go!
- ♪ It's gonna be
one shell of a sight ♪
♪ You know the turtles
got your back ♪
♪ Back, back to the Sewer
♪ Teenage Mutant Ninja Turtles
- Roll call!
Leonardo!
Donatello!
Raphael, Michelangelo!
- ♪ I love bein' a turtle
- ♪ There's a mean,
green team of heroes ♪
♪ That you've never seen
♪ And they're doin'
everything they can ♪
- Let's go!
- ♪ To stop
evil Shredder's plan ♪
♪ Oh yeah,
the turtles are back ♪
♪ Back, back to the Sewer
♪ Teenage Mutant Ninja Turtles
♪ Teenage Mutant
Ninja Turtles ♪
♪ Back, back to the Sewer ♪
- ♪
- And once we find one of Master
Splinter's databits,
we use this device
to store it.
Then we bring it back here
and download it into
our main server.
- Great. So when
do we leave?
- Are you sure about
this, April?
Cyberspace can be
a very dangerous place--
especially with the Shredder
still lurking around in there.
- APRIL: Are you kidding?
I've spent years
on this side of the screen.
I can't wait to see what
it's like on the inside.
Besides, I wanna help.
Master Splinter's been like
a father to me, too, you know?
- I see your point.
- All right then.
Here goes nothing.
Whoa! It's tingly.
- ♪
- Oh.
[laughing]
Whoa.
- Welcome to cyberspace.
Every computer program
and data network
in the entire web has
a manifestation here--
from the biggest database
to the smallest instant message.
- It's amazing.
- Hop on.
There's a cluster of Master
Splinter's databits
straight up this code route.
Hang tight!
- [engine revving]
- ♪
- Check it out.
- CASEY: There's another one.
- [moaning]
No...
- Let's get in
for a closer look.
- ♪
- Looks like it's open season
on Purple Dragons tonight.
- MOHAWK: [groaning]
- No kiddin'.
I'm startin' to lose count.
- Look! Down the side alley.
- HUN: [groaning]
- CASEY: They took
down Hun, too.
Who coulda done this?
- ♪
- GUARD: [groaning]
- [heavy thud]
- [groaning]
- The New York City
central mainframe.
My time in the cyber realm
has shown me another
side to this city--
a side that has grown
dependent on computers
and technology for every
aspect of daily life.
I have studied the mainframe's
weaknesses from the inside.
Their primitive firewalls
will crumble before me.
He who controls the mainframe,
controls the city.
And now I shall bend
it to my will--
so the Foot can rule again!
- [electrical zapping]
- [power grid shutting down]
- ♪
- [vehicles crashing]
- [brakes screeching]
- ♪
- MICHELANGELO & LEONARDO:
[grunts of combat]
- Focus, Mikey.
In randori you have to
learn to think
several moves
ahead of your opponent.
Make him do what you
want him to do
and lead him into a trap.
- I can't think that
far ahead, Leo.
I just improvise,
go with the flow, you know?
- WOMAN: [screaming]
- [vehicles crashing]
- [screeching brakes]
- ♪
- [metal shutters clanking]
- [doors slamming]
- [electricity zapping]
- What's going on?
- PEOPLE: [screaming]
- That doesn't sound good.
Come on!
- ♪
- [train roaring]
- That train isn't
slowing down!
- PASSENGERS:
[screaming]
- It's outta control!
- We have to stop it.
There are people on board.
Quick!
- ♪
- Get to the emergency brake.
I'll knock out the train's
third-rail connector.
- ♪
- [straining]
- [door bells dinging]
- PASSENGERS:
[screaming]
[screaming stops]
- MICHELANGELO:
[screaming]
- ♪
- [metal clanking]
- [grunting]
- ♪
- [gasping]
- [metal clanking]
- LEONARDO: Now, Mikey!
Hit the brake!
- MICHELANGELO:
I'm on it!
- [brakes screeching]
- [gasping]
- [metal cars thud]
- Oh...
It doesn't get
much closer than that.
- Not yet, anyway. Look!
- [loud droning signal]
- [growling]
- ♪
- [electricity zapping]
- [loud droning signal]
- Uh, Donnie? What's that?
- [electrical zapping]
- [loud droning signal]
- The Shredder.
He's somehow infecting
the New York City mainframe
with malicious code.
- APRIL: Oh!
- We have to get back to
the lair and warn the others.
- What about
Master Splinter's databits?
- If we don't stop this thing,
it may put all of Master
Splinter's databits in jeopardy.
Hold on!
- [engine revving]
- ♪
- We've got a problem!
- I'll say. The whole
city's gone berserk.
- DONATELLO:
It's the Shredder.
He's taking over the entire
city's computer infrastructure.
Everything in this city that's
connected to a computer network
is falling under his control.
- What do you
mean "everything"?
- I mean, the electric grid,
rail switches, traffic lights,
security systems, water valves,
telephones, bank vaults.
- Everything that makes
civilized life possible.
Life as we knew it, anyway.
- [horns blaring]
- PEOPLE: [screaming,
shouting]
- [glass shattering]
- New York City
is under cyber attack.
All bridges and tunnels
are closed.
Telephone service
has been disrup--
- [loud droning signal]
- [sirens wailing]
- ♪
- It's everywhere.
- So, why haven't the lair's
computers been affected?
- DONATELLO:
Our critical systems
are on an isolated network--
completely separate
from the city's.
- Good. Then rev up
the cyber portals
so we can take on the Shredder
and end this cyber assault.
- No, the hack is originating
from the outside--
at the city's
central mainframe.
- Then let's head over
there and kick some shell.
- Right. But to get the city's
mainframe back online,
we'll need more
than just brute force.
If we could generate
a kind of low-yield
electromagnetic blast
pulse, however,
we may have a shot.
- I'd agree, only I got no
clue what you just said.
- The blast would disrupt
the mainframe
long enough for us to
upload a worm-killer
that would put a stop
to the Shredder's incursion.
But we'll have to hurry.
There's not much time.
- Exactly how
"not much time" is there?
- At the current
rate of infection,
about 16 minutes.
And after that,
it'll be too late.
- Then we don't
have a moment to waste.
Let's move!
- [tires squealing]
- [engines revving]
- ♪
- [lampposts clanking]
- [tires squealing]
- This isn't gonna cause
any permanent damage
to the city, is it?
- No, the E-M pulse should
force a total reboot.
We'll upload my worm-killer
from a laptop
and then, hopefully,
wipe out the malicious code.
- ♪
- Fools. You dare try
and stop me?
I have a million eyes
and a million fists.
- ♪
- [fire hydrant clanking]
- [glass shattering]
- ALL: [gasping]
- [fire hydrant clanking]
- [metal lid thudding]
- What in the...?
- [fire hydrants clanking]
- [metal lids thudding]
- [fire hydrant clanking]
- [metal lid thudding]
- [gasping, groaning]
- Two down, one to go.
- [electrical zapping]
- [alarm buzzing]
- [thunderous explosions]
- Hold on!
- [engine revving]
- [heavy thud]
- ♪
- [metal clanking]
- APRIL: [groaning]
- ALL: [groaning]
- Something tells
me the Shredder
doesn't want us making
it to that mainframe.
- All the more reason
we have to get there.
Hurry up, this way!
The streets are too dangerous.
- ♪
- Fools!
You cannot escape my reach.
- [electrical zapping]
- [computer beeps]
- ♪
- DONATELLO: The central
mainframe building
is six blocks over,
two blocks down.
- [water roaring]
- Anyone else hear that?
- CASEY & APRIL: Huh?
- [thunderous rush
of water]
- ♪
- Dive!
- [sewer cover clanking]
- ALL: [groaning]
- ♪
- DONATELLO: This is it--
the central
mainframe building.
- Quick, there's
no time to lose.
- DONATELLO:
Careful, guys.
Khan and the Foot could
be behind any corner.
- ♪
- DONATELLO: There's
the central terminal.
- RAPHAEL:
And there's Khan!
- ♪
- LEONARDO: Yeah,
not to mention
more than a few
Foot cronies.
- ♪
- It's over, Khan.
Release the city.
- CYBER SHREDDER:
It is not his to release.
- ♪
- MICHELANGELO:
The Shredder?
He escaped out
of cyberspace?
- But how?
- Who cares?
Now we can put the hurt
on him for real.
- I have long waited
for this moment.
Destroy them!
- ♪
- ALL: [grunts of combat]
- Yes, come to me.
- Pathetic.
You can at least
give me a challenge.
- ♪
- [heavy thud]
- [wall vibrating]
- 'Night. 'Night.
- DONATELLO: All right,
time to disrupt the system
long enough so we can
upload that worm-killer.
Fire in the hole!
- [device beeping]
- What?
- CYBER SHREDDER:
[roaring]
- [energy pulsating]
- CYBER SHREDDER: [roaring]
- April, it's now or never.
- ♪
- Loading the worm-killer now.
- DONATELLO: Which means
your stranglehold
on the city is about to
be over--for good.
- Ya never shoulda
left cyberspace.
- ALL: [grunts of combat]
- ♪
- CYBER SHREDDER: Ahhh!
- LEONARDO: After him!
- ♪
- What is this place?
- The backup power station
for essential city services.
- CYBER SHREDDER: [roaring]
- CASEY: [groaning]
- [energy pulsating]
- Whoa.
- TURTLES: [roaring]
[grunts of combat]
- DONATELLO: [groaning]
- Get outta here!
- RAPHAEL: [groaning]
- And then there was one.
- APRIL: Almost...
almost...
There. All clear.
- ♪
- [power grid surging on]
- [heavy thud, metal whines]
- Huh?
- [electrical zapping]
- CYBER SHREDDER: [roaring]
- MICHELANGELO: [screaming]
- ♪
- CYBER SHREDDER: You are
no match for us.
- [metal creaking]
- What have you done?
- Nothing. That was all
you, shreddy bear.
- CYBER SHREDDER:
[gasping]
[screaming]
- [electrical zapping]
- [groaning]
- [explosion]
- ♪
- [shallow groan]
- Nice improvising, Mikey.
- You know me.
Just go with the flow.
- Master Khan and the Foot--
they took off running.
- And the Shredder's
a crispy critter.
- We did it.
We finally stopped
the Shredder and the Foot.
- MAN: This way.
I think they're in here.
- MAN #2: Come on.
- [sirens wailing]
- And now we should
get outta here.
- RAPHAEL: Hey, it wouldn't
be savin' the city,
and takin' down
our arch nemesis,
if we didn't have to disappear
into the shadows.
- ♪
- [electrical zapping]
♪