Donatello: COUNTLESS MILES
OF CYBERSPACE COMBED OVER.
INNUMEROUS LINES
OF PROGRAMMING CODE SCOURED.
A MYRIAD OF BYTES, NODES,
AND CACHES SCRUTINIZED.
BUT FINALLY, 92,643
NANOSCOPIC DATA BITS LATER,
OUR FATHER
IS ABOUT TO BE WHOLE AGAIN.
UH, THAT'S ASSUMING
THIS WORKS.
IT HAS TO WORK.
I DESIGNED THE CYBERMAT PORTAL
TO CONVERT MATTER INTO CODE,
SO BY REVERSING THE POLARITY OF
THE DEFAULT STASIS APPLICATION,
CODE SHOULD BE ABLE TO BE
CONVERTED BACK INTO MATTER.
SOUNDS LIKE YOU'VE GOT
EVERYTHING COVERED, DONNIE.
YEAH.
ESPECIALLY THE BIG WORDS.
WELL, HERE GOES.
FATHER!
FATHER!FATHER!
[ LAUGHTER ]
[ SIGHS ]
[ Laughing ]
ALL RIGHT! YEAH!
WE WERE SO WORRIED.
HOW MANY FINGERS
AM I HOLDING UP?
ARE YOU OKAY?
HOW YOU FEELING?
I FEEL...
WHOLE...
AND HAPPY TO BE HOME...
THOUGH A BIT LIGHT-HEADED.
THE MATTER CONVERSION PROCESS
IS STRESSFUL, FATHER.
LET'S GET YOU SOME REST.
Serling: REST?
HE NEEDS TO PACK.
WE'RE SCHEDULED TO DEPART
FOR THE WEDDING IN MINUTES.
OH.
AND WELCOME BACK, SIR.
UH, WEDDING?
YEAH, CASEY AND APRIL'S.
ABOUT TIME, RIGHT?
MY SONS,
LET US CELEBRATE OUR REUNION.
AND I CAN THINK
OF NO BETTER PLACE TO DO SO
THAN THE UNION
OF CASEY AND APRIL.
FATHER, IF YOU'RE UP FOR IT,
SO AM I.
LET'S FINALLY PUT THE PROBLEMS
OF CYBERSPACE BEHIND US.
[ BEEPING ]
IT'S NINJA TIME!
♪ IN THE CITY, ON THE SCENE,
UNDERGROUND, OR IN BETWEEN ♪
♪ THERE'S A MEAN, GREEN TEAM OF
HEROES LIKE YOU'VE NEVER SEEN ♪
♪ AND WHEN THE VILLAINS
AND TURTLES FIGHT ♪
♪ IT'S GONNA BE
ONE SHELL OF A SIGHT ♪
♪ YOU KNOW
THE TURTLES GOT YOUR ♪
♪ BACK, BACK TO THE SEWER
♪ TEENAGE MUTANT NINJA TURTLES
ROLL CALL!
♪ LEONARDO, DONATELLO
♪ RAFAEL, MICHELANGELO
♪ I LOVE BEING A TURTLE
♪ THERE'S A MEAN, GREEN TEAM OF
HEROES LIKE YOU'VE NEVER SEEN ♪
♪ DOIN' EVERYTHING THEY CAN
♪ TO STOP EVIL SHREDDER'S PLAN
♪ OH, YEAH, THE TURTLES ARE
♪ BACK, BACK TO THE SEWER
♪ TEENAGE MUTANT NINJA TURTLES
♪ TEENAGE
MUTANT NINJA TURTLES ♪
♪ BACK TO THE SEWER
Raphael: CASEY'S GRANDMA'S
FARMHOUSE, HERE WE COME!
YOU KNOW, RAPH,
SOME PEOPLE HEAD TO THE COUNTRY
FOR A SLOWER PACE OF LIFE.
SORRY, BRO,
BUT I AIN'T SOME PEOPLE.
I'M THE BEST MAN.
I GOT DUTIES, LIKE TEACHING
CASEY HOW TO TIE A TIE...
WHICH, MAY TAKE A WHILE
SEEING AS HOW THAT AIN'T ONE
OF MY BETTER NINJA SKILLS.
MAN, SERLING,
I AM SO LOOKING FORWARD TO THIS.
I LOVE WEDDINGS.
WHEN HAVE YOU EVER BEEN
TO A WEDDING?
BEEN TO? NEVER.
SEEN ON TV?
ALL THE TIME.
EVERY SERIES EVENTUALLY DOES
A WEDDING EPISODE, DUDE.
I'M NOT PICKING UP
ANY VIRTUAL FLUCTUATIONS
OR DISTORTIONS, MASTER.
THE DIGITAL-TO-PHYSICAL
CONVERSION
HAS BEEN A COMPLETE SUCCESS.
I AM GLAD TO HEAR IT,
MY SON.
HEY, GUYS.
WE'RE HERE.
[ HORN HONKS ]
THEY'RE HERE!
AND SO IS MASTER SPLINTER.
IT'S SO GOOD TO SEE YOU.
THIS MAKES OUR WEDDING
EVEN MORE SPECIAL.
PERFECT, EVEN.
SENSEI, YOU LOOK LIKE
A MILLION BUCKS.
HEH. BETTER THAN
A MILLION PIECES, RIGHT?
COME ON IN, EVERYONE.
TAKE A LOAD OFF.
I'M TELLIN' YA, THE SHREDDER
NEVER STOOD A CHANCE.
YES, I HAVE HEARD.
MY SONS HAVE MADE
THEIR FATHER QUITE PROUD.
[ BOTH CHUCKLING ]
HOW ABOUT YOU,
MASTER SPLINTER?
WHAT WAS CYBERSPACE LIKE?
IT WAS...STRANGE.
I HAD NO SINGLE SENSE OF SELF,
BUT, RATHER, A MULTITUDE
OF THOUGHTS AND FEELINGS.
Splinter:
COMMON TO THEM ALL, HOWEVER,
WAS A LONGING
TO RETURN TO MY FAMILY.
WELL, DONNIE
SURE TOOK CARE OF THAT.
YEAH, THAT BIG OLD BRAIN
OF HIS
WAS WORKING OVERTIME TO GET YOU
OUT OF THERE SAFE AND SOUND.
[ POUNDING ON DOOR ]
HUH?
HUH?HUH?
ARE YOU GUYS
EXPECTING SOMEONE?
NO, NONE OF THE GUESTS ARE DUE
TO ARRIVE UNTIL THE MORNING.
[ POUNDING CONTINUES ]
[ WHOOSH! ]
MA?
CASEY!
[ SIGHS ]
THAT'S ASSUMING CASEY GOT THE
DATES ON THE INVITATIONS RIGHT.
WELL, UH,
ALL THOSE LETTERS AND NUMBERS
SEEM THE SAME WHEN YOU'RE
WRITIN' IN CALLIGRAPHY.
[ BOTH GROAN ]
HEY, CUZ.
UHH!
WHAT'S SHAKING, APRIL?
WHA-- UH...
Casey's Mom:
DON'T YOU WORRY, CASEY.
I TOLD YOUR COUSIN SID
IF HE TELLS A SOUL
ABOUT YOUR SPECIAL FRIENDS,
I'LL BUST HIS KNEECAPS.
WHAT A LONG JOURNEY
THIS HAS BEEN.
[ PBHT! ]Together: ANCIENT ONE?!
GUESS I'D BETTER GO GET
THE SPARE BLANKETS.
BLANKETS?
WHAT A TREAT.
PROFESSOR?!PROFESSOR?!PROFESSOR?!
WHAT UP, GUYS?ANGEL?
SEE?
THIS IS WHY I LOVE WEDDINGS.
I HEAR YOU.
NOTHING BEATS BEING SURROUNDED
BY FRIENDS AND FAMILY.
[ INDISTINCT CONVERSATION ]
WE HAVE THEIR POSITION,
AND SOON,
IN THE NAME OF THE MASTER,
WE SHALL HAVE THEIR HEADS!
Raphael: I'M TELLING YOU --
THE RABBIT GOES IN THE HOLE,
AROUND THE TREE, AND THEN...
VOILà!
UH.
HUH?
UH,
YOU SURE THIS IS RIGHT?
UH, GUYS?
THE CEREMONY
STARTS IN AN HOUR.
SO, GETTING NERVOUS YET?
ME? NERVOUS?
COME ON!
I'VE TAKEN ON ENTIRE
STREET GANGS SINGLE-HANDEDLY...
GONE MANO A MANO WITH SOME
OF THE BIGGEST BADDIES
IN THE CRIMINAL UNDERWORLD...
FOUGHT MONSTERS, MUTANTS,
AND ALIENS.
I MEAN, YOU THINK
I'LL GET NERVOUS
JUST 'CAUSE TODAY
I'M GETTING MAR--
MAR-- MAR--
OH.
WHOA, THERE!
NICE GOING, BEST MAN.
HEY, JUST BE GLAD NONE
OF THOSE MONSTERS OR MUTANTS
EVER PROPOSED.
OKAY, APRIL.
YOUR VEIL IS ALL READY.
I ALSO PUT TOGETHER
THE BOUTONNIERES
AND FLORAL ARRANGEMENTS --
ONE FOR EVERY GUEST.
THANKS, MIKEY.
YOU'RE THE BEST BRIDESMAID
EVER.
BRIDESMAID?!
GIVE A TURTLE A LITTLE RESPECT.
I'M THE MAID OF HONOR.
YAAAHH!
SO, HOW DO I LOOK?
AHH!
[ TING! ]
BEAUTIFUL!
RIGHT THIS WAY,
LADIES AND GENTLEMEN...
AND, UH, NONE OF THE ABOVES.
INTERDIMENSIONAL...
OH, I GIVE UP.
[ INDISTINCT CONVERSATIONS ]
DONATELLO.
GOOD TO SEE YOU.
WHERE IS YOUR GIFT, GEN?
GIFTS, USAGI?
WE WERE SUPPOSED TO
BRING GIFTS?
WELL, I'M SURE...
HISOMI WON'T MIND
IF I SHARE HIS.
[ HUMMING ]
[ WHOOSH! ]
[ LAUGHS NERVOUSLY ]
I GUESS, UH, YOU'RE HISOMI.
CAPTAIN MORTU,
I'M PLEASED TO REPORT
THAT THERE IS NO SUSHI BAR
AT THE RECEPTION.
THANK GOODNESS.
WE WOULDN'T WANT A REPEAT
OF WHAT HAPPENED LAST TIME.
I STILL SMELL LIKE
SOY SAUCE.
[ CRYING ]
YOU OKAY, LEATHERHEAD?
OH, YES.
I'M FINE, ANGEL.
I JUST ALWAYS CRY AT WEDDINGS.
WELL, THAT'S
JUST ABOUT EVERYONE.
YOU GUYS SEEN APRIL?
I HAVEN'T SEEN APRIL.
SHE'S NOT HERE.
YOU THINK
SHE'S HAVIN' SECOND THOUGHTS?
AW, I KNEW
THIS WOULD HAPPEN.
EASY, MY SON.
IT IS TRADITION FOR THE GROOM
NOT TO SEE THE BRIDE
BEFORE THE CEREMONY.
SHE IS PREPARING HERSELF
IN THE FARMHOUSE.
I WILL FETCH HER.
HMM.
[ GASPS ]
THE FOOT!
I MUST WARN THE OTHERS.
OH! OH.
YOU WILL WARN NO ONE,
RODENT.
[ SNAPS ]
[ GRUNTS ]
Man:
I WONDER WHAT'S TAKING SO LONG.
[ INDISTINCT CONVERSATIONS ]
April: Psst! GUYS?
EVERYTHING OKAY?
APRIL?
WHOA...BABE.
YOU LOOK BEAU-- BEA--
BEA-- UGH.
WHOA!
EASY, KILLER.
SORRY FOR THE DELAY.
MASTER SPLINTER
WENT TO FIND YOU.
YOU HAVEN'T SEEN HIM?
NO.
I WONDER
WHERE HE COULD --
[ GROANING ]
WHOA!
MASTER SPLINTER!
[ INDISTINCT TALKING ]
MASTER SPLINTER...
HE'S HERE.
HE'S --
[ COUGHING ]
WHAT THE SHELL'S GOING ON?
YOUR LONG-AWAITED DEMISE.
Donatello: THE SHREDDER?
[ GRUNTS ]
[ GASPS ]
ATTACK!
HA!
I DON'T REMEMBER GETTING
YOUR RSVP, BUCKET-FOR-BRAINS.
YEAH. LIKE, DIDN'T WE FRY YOU UP
EXTRA-CRISPY-STYLE?
MY BODY PERHAPS.
BUT THE ELECTRIC CURRENT
YOU SOUGHT TO DESTROY ME WITH
DID NOT DAMAGE
MY DIGITAL CORE.
DIGITAL CORE?
YES.
I ESCAPED BACK TO CYBERSPACE
WHERE I WAS ABLE TO ABSORB
THE MASSIVE INFLUX OF ENERGY.
ENERGY THAT ALLOWED ME
TO RECONSTITUTE MYSELF
TO BECOME
MORE POWERFUL THAN EVER.
YEAH.
I'M KIND OF GETTIN' THAT.
THEN IT WAS SIMPLY A MATTER
OF INFECTING ONE
OF THE RAT'S DATA BITS
WITH A LINE OF CODE THAT,
ONCE CONVERTED INTO MATTER,
BECAME A HOMING BEACON...
WHICH LED ME RIGHT TO YOU...
AND THIS MOST
AUSPICIOUS OCCASION.
[ GASPS ]
OH.
[ WHISTLES ]
YOU CRASHED THE WRONG WEDDING,
KHAN!
DONNIE, WE'LL HANDLE
THE SHREDDER.
GET MASTER SPLINTER
OUT OF HERE.
YOU'LL HANDLE NOTHING.
[ GASPS ]
YOUR ATTEMPTS TO DESTROY ME
HAVE ONLY MADE ME FASTER...
STRONGER!
AND IT WILL NOW COST YOU
EVERYTHING.
IT IS TIME.
[ GASPING, SCREAMING ]
FAREWELL, WORMS.
OH, DEAR!
NO!
NO!NO!NO!
[ LAUGHS EVILLY ]
AND NOW IT IS YOUR TURN
TO PERISH.
[ GRUNTING ]
WAIT. LOOK!
SOMETHING'S STILL MOVING
IN THERE.
DONNIE, CHECK IT OUT.
MIKEY AND I
WILL BACK UP RAPH.
YOUR BROTHER IS WISE TO RUN.
STILL, HE ONLY POSTPONES
THE INEVITABLE.
I WILL DESTROY YOU ALL.
EVERYONE OUT!
HURRY!
[ INDISTINCT SHOUTING ]
COME ON.
WE'VE GOT TO GET MASTER SPLINTER
BACK TO THE HAULER.
IT'S SAFE, AND IT MIGHT JUST
GIVE US OUR ONLY CHANCE
AT BEATING THE SHREDDER.
[ GASPS ]
FINISH THEM.
THE SHREDDER SAID
HE HAD A DIGITAL CORE.
IF WE CAN GET A SAMPLING
OF THAT CORE'S CODING SIGNATURE,
WE MIGHT BE ABLE TO USE IT
AGAINST HIM.
Serling: A DIGITAL CORE?
BUT I THOUGHT IN THIS WORLD,
THE SHREDDER
WAS MADE ENTIRELY OF MATTER.
SO DID I.
BUT SINCE THIS SHREDDER
WAS BORN OUT OF VIRAL'S BODY,
HE MUST HAVE INHERITED
SOME OF HER DIGITAL PROPERTIES.
SO HOW DO WE GET THIS SAMPLING,
MY SON?
WITH THIS!
THE SHREDDER INFECTED ONE
OF YOUR DATA BITS
SO THAT, WHEN CONVERTED INTO
MATTER, IT BECAME THIS BEACON.
IF WE COULD CONVERT IT
BACK INTO CODE,
WE'LL HAVE OUR SAMPLE
AND ALL THE DATA WE NEED
TO DESTROY THE SHREDDER THE SAME
WAY WE DESTROYED VIRAL...
WITH YOUR DECOMPILING BLAST.
SO, WHAT DO YOU THINK
THE ODDS ARE
OF US GETTIN' THROUGH THIS?
STATISTICALLY SPEAKING...
BAD.
YEAH? WELL I'D SAY THEY JUST GOT
A LITTLE BIT BETTER.
LOOK!
IT'S THE JUSTICE FORCE.
SORRY WE'RE LATE.
OH, AND CONGRATULATIONS
FROM ALL OF US.
AAH!
THIS IS YOUR END.
Splinter: UNHAND MY SONS.
WHAT?! HA!
WHAT COULD YOU POSSIBLY DO
TO MAKE ME?
THIS!
PATHETIC.
YOU ARE POWERLESS
TO DEFEAT ME.
I CAN'T GET A SHOT
THROUGH THAT SHIELD.
IT'S IMPERVIOUS
TO THE DECOMPILER BEAM.
BUT PERHAPS IT IS NOT IMPERVIOUS
TO FLESH AND BLOOD.
GRRR!
I WILL NEVER FALL TO YOU,
RAT.
IT WAS NOT MY AIM
TO MAKE YOU FALL.
HUH?
NO!
[ SCREAMS ]
NICE SHOT!
WAY TO GO, DONNIE!
Casey: HEY, RAPH.
I THINK
I FINALLY FIGURED OUT
HOW TO TIE THIS THING.
CASEY!
NOW, THEN, LET'S NOT LET A FEW
BAD APPLES RUIN ALL THE FUN.
I BELIEVE THERE'S A WEDDING
TO BE HAD.
YES.
BUT PERHAPS...OUTSIDE.
[ CHUCKLES ]
[ SNIFFLING ]
NO MATTER HOW MANY TIMES
I'VE BEEN TO THIS WEDDING,
IT ALWAYS MAKES ME CRY.
AND SO, BY THE POWERS VESTED
IN ME BY PLANET D'HOONNIB,
IT GIVES ME GREAT PLEASURE
TO PRONOUNCE YOU, CASEY JONES,
AND YOU, APRIL O'NEIL,
MAN AND WIFE.
YOU MAY KISS THE BRIDE.
[ CHEERS AND APPLAUSE ]
YEAH!
HA HA HA!
CAPTIONS PAID FOR BY
4KIDS PRODUCTIONS, INC.