- ♪
- There's a cluster
of Master Splinter's data bytes
straight ahead.
- We see them on the scanner,
Donnie.
We're right behind you.
- Or right in front of you.
[laughs]
Eat my cyber dust!
- I don't think so.
- ♪
- Time to shift this
into the next gear.
- Guys, something is wrong
with the cyber mat portal.
- What do you mean, April?
What is it?
- It's the hardware.
It's overheating.
I can't stop it.
You'd better get out of there,
and fast.
I'm opening up the cyber portal.
- Let's move.
Go! Go!
- Whoa!
Ah!
- [grunting]
- [explosion]
- APRIL: Everything's
going haywire.
Uh!
- Oh, dear!
- Quick, don't let it spread.
- I can't believe this.
It was hard enough
retrieving Master Splinter's
data bytes before.
But now...it's
gonna be impossible.
- It's ninja time!
- ♪ In the city, on the scene,
underground, and in between ♪
♪
♪ There's a mean, green team
of heroes ♪
♪ That you've never seen
♪ And when the villains
and turtles fight ♪
♪ It's gonna be
one shell of a sight ♪
♪ You know the turtles
got your back ♪
♪ Back, Back to the Sewer
♪ Teenage Mutant Ninja Turtles
- Roll call!
- ♪ Leonardo, Donatello
♪ Raphael, Michelangelo
- ♪ I love bein' a turtle
- ♪ There's a mean, green team
of heroes ♪
♪ That you've never seen
♪ And they're doin'
everything they can ♪
♪ To stop evil Shredder's plan
♪ Oh yeah,
the turtles are back ♪
♪ Back, back to the Sewer
♪ Teenage Mutant Ninja Turtles
♪ Back to the Sewer ♪
- ♪
- I can't believe the cyber mat
just blew.
- We're just lucky
that we made it out in time.
It was a close call.
- More like a major meltdown.
- It doesn't make sense.
I just ran a diagnostic
before we went in.
All the cyber mat's systems
checked out normal.
- I know.
It must have been some sort
of technical abdominally
that we overlooked.
These things
just happen sometimes.
- [sighs]
I guess I know
what I'm doing tonight.
- You want any help, Donnie?
- Uh, no thanks, guys.
April, Serling and I
should be able to handle it.
- All right, then.
We should probably
hit the rooftops anyway.
- Yeah, see what's shaking
in our fair city.
- Right, make sure Khan
and the Purple Dragons
aren't up to any trouble.
Sounds like fun.
You can count me in.
- ♪
- APRIL: So what do we do first
to fix this, Donnie?
I'm a little unclear
on the details.
But if you walk me through it,
I know I could help.
- Simply relay
your instructions.
- [bug buzzes]
- [grunting]
- ♪
- Easy there, Mikey.
- What's with all
the fancy moves?
- Just because
we're on pump patrol
doesn't mean we can't do it
in style.
- Yeah.
But you don't have any style.
- I beg to differ,
shell breath.
Check this out.
- ♪
- A fire winder.
A flying ninja.
What's up, moon?
And return to Earth.
Huh?
Guys!
- Lame!
- Uh, I thought you did great,
Mickey.
- [laughs]
- Mickey?
Wait up for me!
- ♪
- My Lord Shredder,
I have good news.
- Speak, Khan.
- Everything has come to pass
exactly as you predicted.
I have our crews
working as fast as they can.
I am pleased
that all the information
I had accumulated on the turtles
was at last put to good use.
- Double your efforts, Khan.
This diversion is not perfect.
And it will not be long until
the turtles realize our scheme.
- [cat purrs]
- [grunts]
- Nice try, Raph,
but you couldn't shake us.
Now it's my turn.
See if you can
follow these moves.
- ♪
- Hu, piece of cake.
- No, no, no.
Brains before stupid.
- [grunts]
- ♪
- Hard to improve on perfection,
but bring it on
if you think you got the stuff.
- After you.
- Uh, consider
the stuff brought.
- ♪
This is too easy.
What the--
Ah!
- Mikey!
- Ahh!
- ♪
- Aaah!
- Hold on!
- Ah!
- Gotcha!
Nice and easy, Mikey.
Just go nice and easy.
After a fall like that,
you might feel a little wobbly
on your feet.
- [groans]
- Whoa.
You okay?
What happened?
- I--I was jumping and--and
the building...moved.
- BOTH: [laughing]
- I'm serious, guys.
- Okay, okay,
enough goofing around.
Let's keep moving.
We're supposed to be
on patrol, remember?
- Shake it off, bro.
You just misjudged it.
It's no biggie.
- [grunts]
- ♪
- APRIL: Just so I'm clear, at
what ion junction did you solder
the reflex convertor
into the triple capacitor?
- What is the precise frequency
of that sub-generator?
- Is there a base atomic order
that the transistors must fit
into in order to synchronize
with the carbon retainers?
- [grunts]
Listen.
I appreciate
that you're trying to help,
but maybe a few less questions
and a little more helping.
Or just let me do it on my own.
- Fine.
You just keep at it.
I won't get in your way, Donald.
- Donald?
- [bug buzzing]
- ♪
- [indistinct chatter]
- Purple Dragons.
And it looks like
they're up to no good.
Let's try and get in closer
so we can see
what we're up against.
- Oh, I'm getting up close,
all right.
And personal!
- Hey, save some for me!
- [grunting]
- Patience is a virtue that
my brothers just don't have.
- Oh, well.
Gondola!
- [grunting]
- [grunts]
- ♪
- [groaning]
- Where do you think
you're going?
Yeah, that's what I thought.
- [grunting]
- Guys, what are you
looking so scared for?
We got 'em
right where we want 'em.
Ah!
- [sizzles]
- Casey?
No!
- [yelling]
- After 'em!
- Ah!
- You punks are gonna--huh?
What the shell?
There's no one here.
- There's no one
out here either.
No sign of 'em.
Casey.
- [brakes squeak]
- April?
- I've been looking
all over for you guys.
Get in.
- April, Casey, he's--
- He's gone. They--they--
- Wasted him.
Vaporized him.
- Oh, okay.
Guess it was bound to happen
sooner or later.
- April, did you
hear what we said?
- You betcha.
- [tires squeal]
- April, you're headed
right for that wall!
- What wall?
What are you talking about--
[in man's voice] Raphael?
- ALL: Aaah!
- [crash]
- ♪
- [groaning]
- Does anyone else smell smoke?
- Get April out of the front.
- She's gone.
- Then we should be, too.
- Wait, now she's back.
- April!
- [explosion]
- April.
- [siren wailing]
- Come on.
- She was in there.
She--she--
- But that can't be.
She wasn't before.
- What the shell
is going on here?
- None of it makes any sense.
- It doesn't.
None of it.
Unless...we're not
where we think we are.
- Come again.
- The things that have happened,
they're so unreal.
Those Purple Dragons
just disappearing
into thin air like that.
- Yeah.
And come to think of it, anyone
else here Casey's voice
come out
of April's mouth earlier?
- And I'm telling you, that
building really did move
when I tried that jump.
- All these little glitches,
they can't all be coincidence.
There has to be an explanation.
- Glitches?
What are saying, Leo?
We're in one of Mikey's
video games?
- No.
But...what if
we're still in cyberspace?
- But how?
We came out through the portal.
- No, no, wait.
What if it just
seemed like we did?
Think about it.
There are all kinds of false
realities in cyberspace.
Who's to say that cyber portal
we went through
wasn't one of 'em?
- Right.
Along with everything
that's happened since then.
- But if we were still
in cyberspace, then we could
manifest our cybernaut armor
right here.
Right now.
- There's only one way
to find out.
[groaning]
- [machine buzzing]
- Uh!
What are we waiting for?
It's real!
I mean, not real.
- Then it was all fake?
Casey getting vaporized?
April in that explosion?
- The cyber mat melting down.
Oh, no.
- Uh, you wanna share
with the rest of the class, Leo?
- Think about it.
Right now, Donnie's putting all
of his technical expertise
to work rebuilding the cyber mat
portal from the ground up.
- So?
Who needs a cyber portal?
And who would go
to all the trouble of creating
this false reality to get
the blueprints for one?
- BOTH: The Shredder!
- We have to warn Don,
or The Shredder will have
all the information he needs
to have The Foot
build his own portal.
One that works this time.
Donnie!
Donnie, can you hear me?
You have to stop rebuilding
the cyber mat portal.
Donatello!
- You cannot reach him.
And you will not
leave here alive.
- Funny, I was about
to tell you the same thing.
- ♪
- Is that the best you can do?
- Nah, this is.
[grunt]
- Ah!
- [explosion]
- Ha, ha, almost done.
- Indeed.
And all your hard work
is quite appreciated, Donatello.
- [bug buzzing]
- ♪
- The cyber mat portal
is nearly complete, Master Khan.
- ♪
- [grunting]
You will not stop me!
Ahhh!
- I beg to differ, Shred Head!
Ah!
>> Ha!
Ha!
- SHREDDER: [evil laughing]
- Wait!
This is exactly
what The Shredder wants.
- Ugh!
- What?
For us to kick his butt?
- No!
To keep us from warning Donnie.
- Mikey's right.
Forget The Shredder.
We have to move.
- Fools, you forget
where you are.
Any terrain on which you flee
is a weapon for me
to destroy you with!
Khan, what is the progress
on the cyber mat device?
- We are very close, my master.
- Open it as soon as possible!
The turtles
have learned of our plan.
If they are able to warn
their brother, all will be lost!
Ha!
- TURTLES: Ah!
- Oh, guys, I don't think
we're gonna be warning anyone.
- ♪
- This is gonna be close.
- And every second counts.
Punch it!
- Worms!
There is no escape!
- Faster, we have
to get to Donnie!
- Hate to break it to you, Leo,
but no matter how fast we go,
The Shredder's cyber search
goes faster.
Ugh!
- Ah!
Ahhh!
- I ain't going down like this.
- Follow Raph's lead!
- Works for me.
- Faster!
It's gaining again!
- RAPH: There's no losing
this thing.
- Uh, what are we in for
this time?
- Trouble.
Big trouble.
Look.
How in the shell are we supposed
to get to get to Donnie
with that thing in the way?
- By thinking like cybernauts.
This isn't the real world,
remember?
If The Shredder can move
mountains here,
then we should be able
to split one.
- Yeah.
It's just a matter of being
the bigger, badder megabyte.
- Then let's roll!
[grunting]
- All right, you guys,
let's do this!
- [explosion]
- Did you see that?
We smacked that cyber heap
so hard,
it took down The Shredder's
whole fake reality.
- Oh, yeah.
We got some serious
cyber skills.
- Donnie, did you finish work
on the equipment?
- Uh?
- Donatello,
we're still in cyberspace.
Do you understand?
- What?
What's going on?
What are you saying?
- The Shredder was using you.
- To get the blueprints
for the cybernaut portal.
Did you finish it?
- Nearly.
But no.
- [machine beeps]
- APRIL: Guys!
Guys, come in.
Are you there?
- We're here, April.
- Thank goodness.
I've been trying
to reach you for hours.
- It's a long story.
Can you get us out of here?
- APRIL: Opening a portal now.
- Come on!
- ♪
- [laughing]
- You guys had me worried sick.
I lost all communication
with you.
- You're alive!
You're alive!
- We'll tell you
the whole story.
But the bottom line is--
- It's great to be
back in reality.
- ♪
- SHREDDER: [laughing]
Khan, is it complete?
- Yes, my master.
With the energy signal
you just sampled
from the turtle's exit portal,
we have been able
to finish construction
of the cyber mat portal,
even without
the final specifications.
- Excellent.
And then only one thing remains.
Activate the portal, Khan!
Activate it now!
- ♪
- I live.
I live!
I, The Shredder, have risen.
And the world will now suffer!
[evil laughing]
- ♪