[ ELECTRICITY CRACKLING ]
WHOA!
WHAT HAPPENED?
WHERE AM I?
[ GROANS ]
Cody: DO YOU NEED A BREAK,
DONATELLO?
Donatello: NOPE. NOT UNLESS
YOU DO, LITTLE NINJA.
HEY CODY, COULD YOU PASS ME
THE IONIZED PIVOT WRENCH?
SURE THING, DONNY.
Serling:
NO, NO, ALLOW ME.
PERHAPS I CAN FETCH YOU BOTH
AN ESPRESSO, AS WELL.
ANYTHING TO BE OF ASSISTANCE.
YOU KNOW, SERLING,
SOMETIMES I THINK
YOU'RE LOOKING FORWARD
TO US GETTING HOME
EVEN MORE THAN WE ARE.
LIKE YOU'RE NOT
GONNA MISS US!
I MEAN, RAPH
I CAN UNDERSTAND BUT --
WISE GUY.
THE TURTLES.
NOW I REMEMBER.
I AM STILL INSIDE
THAT INSUFFERABLE ROBOT,
WHERE THOSE CRETINS USED
THAT DECOMPILER PROGRAM
TO TEAR ME APART BIT BY BIT...
...OR SO THEY THOUGHT.
IT HAS TAKEN SOME TIME,
BUT MY ADVANCED
FAIL-SAFE SYSTEMS
HAVE FINALLY REPAIRED ME.
AND NOW THAT I AM 97.005%
RECONSTITUTED,
THE TURTLES WILL PAY!
Cody: WE DID IT!WHAT?
FINALLY!
YOU GUYS CAN GO HOME!
THE TIME WINDOW
IS UP AND RUNNING AGAIN.
TIME WINDOW?
HMM...
AND PERHAPS MY WINDOW
OF OPPORTUNITY
FOR REVENGE!
[ LAUGHS EVILLY ]
IT'S NINJA TIME!
♪ FOUR TEENAGE TURTLES
SURFED IN ♪
♪ ON A WAVE FROM THE PAST
♪ IT'S LIKE
THE FUTURE'S A PARTY ♪
♪ THAT THESE BROTHERS
JUST CRASHED ♪
♪ DON'T KNOW WHEN
THEY'LL GO HOME ♪
♪ HOW LONG THE GOOD TIMES
WILL LAST ♪
♪ BUT JUST STICK AROUND
AND SEE THESE TURTLES GO ♪
♪ FAST FORWARD
♪ LEONARDO, DONATELLO
♪ RAPHAEL, MICHELANGELO
♪ TEENAGE MUTANT NINJA TURTLES
♪ FAST FORWARD
IT'S NINJA TIME!
♪ THIS FUTURE STUFF
IS SO STRANGE ♪
♪ TIME TO GET REARRANGED
♪ BUT THE MORE THINGS CHANGE
♪ THE MORE THEY ALL STAY
THE SAME ♪
♪ STILL KICKING BUTT
AND PLAYING VIDEO GAMES ♪
♪ DRIVING EVERYONE NUTS,
THIS FUTURE'S REALLY INSANE ♪
♪ FAST FORWARD
GET OUT OF MY WAY!
IT'S SO NOT YESTERDAY.
♪ FAST FORWARD
IT'S THE ONLY WAY TO PLAY!
GUESS WE'RE HERE TO STAY.
♪ TEENAGE MUTANT NINJA TURTLES
♪ FAST FORWARD
Cody:
ALL RIGHT, GUYS,
DON AND I
HAVE SET THE TIME WINDOW
TO GET YOU AS CLOSE
TO YOUR OWN TIME AS POSSIBLE.
[ MICHELANGELO GRUNTING ]
I HOPE I DIDN'T
FORGET ANYTHING.
LET'S SEE...
HELIX. HELIX 2. HELIX 3.
HELIX 3: TURBO EDITION.
HELIX 4. HELIX 4H.
NO, MIKEY, WE'RE NOT
BRINGING ANYTHING BACK,
INCLUDING OUR WEAPONS.
WE CAN'T POLLUTE
THE TIME STREAM.
YES, YOU'VE DONE
QUITE ENOUGH OF THAT ALREADY.
[ SMOOCHES ]
BON VOYAGE!
Cody: WELL,
I SUPPOSE THIS IS GOODBYE.
CODY SAN, THANK YOU
FOR YOUR HOSPITALITY.
THOUGH THIS MAY BE GOODBYE,
WE HAVE FORGED A BOND THAT WILL
STAND THE TEST OF TIME...
...PAST, PRESENT, AND FUTURE.
REMEMBER YOUR TEACHINGS,
LITTLE NINJA.
WELL,
GUESS THIS IS IT.
TAKE CARE, GUYS.
I WON'T EVER FORGET YOU.
AND WE WON'T
FORGET YOU, CODY.
THANKS
FOR EVERYTHING.
REMEMBER
THE NINJA CODE.
WE'RE GONNA
MISS YOU, KID.
SO LONG.
[ ELECTRICITY CRACKLING ]AAH!
SERLING, WHAT'S WRONG?
[ SPEAKING INDISTINCTLY ]
WHAT'S HAPPENING?
SOME...SORT OF...V-VIRUS
IS OVERRIDING MY...SYSTEM.
SERLING!
Viral: NOT JUST SOMEVIRUS,
YOU MISERABLE DROID,
BUT THE QUEEN OF ALL VIRUSES!
[ LAUGHS EVILLY ]
NO! STOP!
AAH! AAAAH!
GUYS?
SERLING?
AAAH!
AAAH!AAAH!AAAH!
ANYBODY SEE THAT?
JUST AS WE ENTERED
THE TIME WINDOW,
IT LOOKED LIKE A SURGE
OF ENERGY OR AN EXPLOSION.
YES, LEONARDO.
IT WAS MOST DISCONCERTING.
TELL YOU WHAT'S NOT
DISCONCERTING --
HOME SWEET HOME
DEAD AHEAD!
HA HA! YEAH!
WHOA!
WHOA!WHOA!WHOA!
HEY, WHAT'S UP WITH
THE SUDDEN CHANGE OF COURSE?
AND WHAT'S HE DOING HERE?
[ MOANING ]
Donatello: I DON'T KNOW,
BUT I THINK IT HAS
SOMETHING TO DO WITH VIRAL.
LOOK!
[ LAUGHS EVILLY ]
AAAH!
AAAH!AAAH!AAAH!
TIME AND TIME AGAIN YOU TRIED
TO DESTROY ME.
WELL, NOW TIME IS ON MYSIDE!
AND WITH IT,
I AM GOING TO MAKE YOUSUFFER.
[ LAUGHS EVILLY ]
AAH!
AAH!AAH!AAH!
OW!
DONNY,
WHAT JUST HAPPENED?
VIRAL.
SHE MUST HAVE OVERRIDDEN
THE TIME COORDINATES
CODY AND I HAD WORKED OUT.
BUT I HAVE NO IDEA HOW.
I D-D-D-DO.
JUST AS YOU
W-WERE ALL LEAVING,
SHE S-SURGED
OUT OF MY SYSTEM CORE
AND INF-FECTED
THE T-T-TIME WINDOW!
SHE WHAT?!
UH, GUYS?
BUT THAT
WOULD MEAN
THAT SHE'S SOMEHOW
TAKEN CONTROL
OF THE
TEMPORAL STREAM.
GUYS?!
WHICH WOULD EXPLAIN
WHY WE DID NOT MAKE IT HOME...
SERIOUSLY, GUYS?!
...AND ENDED UP HERE.
AND WE'RE NOT ALONE!
[ GROWLING ]
OH, THAT DOESN'T
SOUND GOOD!
[ ROARING ]
PUNY ORGANIC INSECTS!
OVER AND OVER AGAIN
YOU SOUGHT TO DESTROY ME,
TO RIP ME UP
INTO BITS AND BYTES!
WELL NOW, MY LITTLE FRIEND HERE
IS GOING TO RETURN THE FAVOR.
OH, HOW I'M GOING TO
SAVOR THIS.
SERLING,
BLAST THAT LIZARD!
I WOULD,
BUT I'M AFRAID THAT JUST BEFORE
VIRAL LEFT MY INTERFACE,
SHE DISABLED
ALL OF MY DEFENSE SYSTEMS.
OH!
[ CRYING ]
LEAVE YOUR WEAPONS HERE.
WOULDN'T WANT TO POLLUTE
THE TIME STREAM.
GOOD CALL, DONNY.
[ MOANING ]
[ GRUNTS ]
[ GROWLS ]
AAAAH!
EXTINCTION'S COMING EARLY
FOR YOU, LIZARD BREATH!
TAKE THAT AND THAT AND --
AAAH!
MIKEY!
[ GRUNTS ]
WHOA.
HUH?
THIS IS HOW WE GO OUT,
AS LUNCH?
[ ROARS ]
YEEHAW!
[ LAUGHS ]
HERE'S YOU TREAT.
NOW, GIDDYAP!
WHOO-HOO!
NOW, THAT'S HOW YOU KICK BUTT
OLD-SCHOOL STYLE --
REALLY OLD-SCHOOL.
IT'S LIKE I ALWAYS SAY --
IN THE HANDS OF A NINJA,
ANYTHING CAN BECOME A WEAPON,
INCLUDING MY NEW PAL HERE.
I THINK I'LL CALL HIM
ZOG THE SECOND.
SO, YOU WERE ABLE TO FEND OFF
SOME PEA-BRAINED BEAST.
BUT YOUR TIME TRAVAILS
HAVE JUST BEGUN.
AAH!
AAH!AAH!AAH!
OUCH.
UGH. WHY AM I ALWAYS
ON THE BOTTOM?
WHERE ARE WE NOW?
I THINK YOU MEAN "WHEN."
[ HORSE NEIGHS ]Man: THERE! OVER YONDER!
YOU, STRANGE KNIGHT
AND YOUR BAND OF GREEN FIENDS,
PREPARE TO BE VANQUISHED!
CHARGE!
"STRANGE KNIGHT"?
DOES HE MEAN ME?
RELAX, BUCKET HEAD.
IT'S JUST ONE GUY.
NO SWEAT!
ATTACK!
CHARGE!CHARGE!CHARGE!CHARGE!
ALL RIGHT,
MAYBE A LITTLE SWEAT.
WELCOME TO THE DARK AGES,
TURTLES.
AND FOR YOU, THEY WILL BE
DARK TIMES INDEED.
AAAH!
I CAN'T BELIEVE THIS --
FROM DINO TIMES
TO MEDIEVAL TIMES?!
BELIEVE IT.
AND UNLESS WE FIGURE OUT A WAY
TO TURN THE TABLES ON VIRAL,
IT'S JUST A MATTER OF TIME
BEFORE WE'REHISTORY.
YOU SHALL BE VANQUISHED
FOR THE KING!
AND YOU SHALL BE GETTING OFF
YOUR HIGH HORSE!
WHAT? STOP THAT!
[ RATTLE! ]
HA HA!
ALL HAIL SIR MIKEY THE BOLD!
TALLYHO!
AHH!
I'M NOT PROGRAMMED
FOR THIS.
WAIT A SECOND...
THE DECOMPILER PROGRAM!
DECOMPILER? WHAT?
THE PROGRAM WE USED TO RIP
VIRAL APART IN THE FIRST PLACE.
IT'S STILL UPLOADED
ON SERLING'S MAIN DRIVE.
BUT I THOUGHT VIRAL DISENGAGED
ALL OF SERLING'S WEAPONS!
YES, SHE DID.
BUT IF WE CAN FIND A WAY
TO RE-ENGAGE THEM,
I JUST MAY BE ABLE TO USE THEM
TO GET US HOME.
COME ON!
OH! OH!
IF I CAN JURY-RIG
SOME KIND OF UPLINK MODULE
TO SERLING'S BUFFER GRID,
I SHOULD BE ABLE TO GET
HIS WEAPONS SYSTEMS BACK ONLINE.
RIG AN UPLINK MODULE
TO HIS BUFFER-MA-HUH?
LOOK AROUND, BRAINIAC.
WE'RE IN THE DARK AGES HERE.
WE AIN'T GOT
THAT KIND OF TECH!
NOT HERE WE DON'T.
BUT IF YOU-KNOW-WHO
SENT US TO ANOTHER TIME,
ONE CLOSER TO THE PRESENT...
I'M ON IT!
ON WHAT?
HEY,
STATIC FOR BRAINS!
WHAT? YOU DARE?
THAT'S RIGHT!
I'M TALKING TO YOU,
YOU OVERGROWN ELECTRODE.
IS THIS THE BEST YOU CAN DO?
WHAT'S HE DOING?
YOU CALL THESETOUGH TIMES?
COME ON!
WHY DON'T YOU PUT US SOMETIME
WHERE YOU CAN REALLY
WATCH US SQUIRM?
I DARE YOU TO SEND US
TO WHEN THE BIG BADDY OF ALL,
SHREDDER, WAS AROUND.
SO BE IT, FOOL.
PREPARE TO EXPERIENCE
YOUR ULTIMATE NIGHTMARE.
WHOA!
WHOA!WHOA!WHOA!
FINALLY,
I'M NOT ON THE BOTTOM!
WHOA!
[ GRUNTING ]
ARE WE HOME?
Raphael:
THAT DON'T SOUND LIKE HOME!
WHAT THE SHELL?
MIKEY, WHAT DID YOU SAY
TO VIRAL?
WHEN ARE WE?
I THINK AROUND PRESENT DAY.
AT LEAST, THAT'S WHEN
I ASKED HER TO SEND US.
COURSE, I HAD TO MAKE IT
SOUND DANGEROUS SO...
AH!
SO YOU GOT US SENT TO SOME
TWISTED TIME WITH TWO SHREDDERS?
LOOK, I WAS ONLY
TRYING TO HELP, OKAY?
MAKE THAT THREE!
LOOK OUT!
AAH!
[ POWERS DOWN ]
OKAY, THIS JUST WENT
FROM BAD TO WORSE.
I DON'T BELIEVE
WE'VE BEEN INTRODUCED.
WELCOME, TURTLES,
TO THE NOT-SO-DISTANT FUTURE,
WHERE IT IS TIME
FOR YOU TO PERISH!
YOUR DOOM IS AT HAND, WORMS!
AAH!
THE TURTLES
WILL BE MYPRIZE!
Raphael: GREAT...
THREE SHREDDERS GOING AT IT
IN AN ALL-OUT RUMBLE,
AND WE'RECAUGHT
IN THE MIDDLE.
TIME TO GET OUT OF HERE.
DONNY, WHAT'S IT GONNA TAKE
TO GET SERLING UP AND RUNNING?
AFTER SHREDDER NUMBER THREE
SLASHED RIGHT THROUGH
HIS MAIN CIRCUIT DRIVE?
A MIRACLE.
IT'S AN ADVANCED DROID PART,
TECHNOLOGY FROM 100 YEARS
IN THE FUTURE.
Khan: YOU.
BUT HOW?
I DISPOSED OF YOU MYSELF.
UH [CHUCKLES]
DO WE KNOW YOU?
WHOA.
LEO!
THE SHELLS OF THE TURTLES
WILL BE MYTROPHY!
HMM.
DONNY, THE UTROM SHREDDER!
OF COURSE.
HIS EXOSKELETON.
IT'S MADE
WITH UTROM TECHNOLOGY.
I CAN WORK WITH THAT.
GUYS, WE'VE GOT TO GET
TO THE CIRCUIT DRIVE
INSIDE THE SHREDDER'S
EXOSKELETON.
CRACK HIM OPEN?
NOW YOU'RE TALKING
MY LANGUAGE.
YOU DARE STRIKE
THE ONE TRUE SHREDDER?!
WE'RE NOT MAKING
A LOT OF HEADWAY HERE.
NO JOKE?
YOU MEAN, TAKING
ON OUR ARCHRIVAL
WITHOUT ANY WEAPONS
AIN'T GIVING US AN EDGE?
HMM.
SURELY YOU WOULD RATHER
FOCUS YOUR ATTACKS
ON A SHARED ADVERSARY
THAN EACH OTHER.
AH, THE RAT!
DONATELLO, NOW!
ALL RIGHT, THEN.
HERE GOES NOTHING!
SOMETIMES THE ENEMIES
OF AN ENEMY CAN BE A FRIEND.
YEAH, WELL, THEY AIN'T
LOOKING TOO FRIENDLY NOW!
COME ON. COME ON.
[ POWERS UP ]
DEAR ME!
WHAT HAPPENED?
OH, YOU'RE STILL HERE?
I THOUGHT I'D RID MYSELF
OF YOU MISERABLE MISANTHROPES.
THERE'S NO TIME
TO EXPLAIN.
ARE ALL YOUR SYSTEMS
UP AND RUNNING,
INCLUDING YOUR WEAPONS?
I BELIEVE SO.
THEN OPEN UP.
TURTLE-X MODE. QUICK!
ALL RIGHT, THE DECOMPILER
PROGRAM WORKED ON VIRAL
AS AN ALGORITHM.
TIME TO SEE HOW IT WORKS
AS A BLAST.
BUT FIRST...
[ FOOTSTEPS THUDDING ]
...TO DEAL WITH THE SHREDDERS.
QUICK, EVERYONE GRAB ON!
NOW!
WHAT?!
Donatello:
FIRING DECOMPILER!
JUST WHAT DO YOU THINK
YOU'RE --
AAAH!
NICE WORK, DONNY.
YEAH,
WE'RE ON OUR WAY HOME!
YEAH!
ALL RIGHT!
[ SIREN WAILS ]
HUH?
[ ELECTRICITY CRACKLING ]
OH, NO.
NO, IT CAN'T BE!
AAH!
BUT IT IS,
YOU WRETCHED ORGANIC.
YOU MAY HAVE WEAKENED ME,
BUT NOT BEFORE
I WAS ABLE TO RE-INFECT
THIS PATHETIC PIECE
OF HARDWARE.
AND NOW THAT I HAVE...
NO, THE DECOMPILER!
INSIDE THE TIME STREAM,
WE'RE NOTHING MORE
THAN TEMPORAL DATA FLOWS.
WE'LL BE SCATTERED TO BITS!
CORRECT!
OR DID YOU NOT CALCULATE
FOR THAT?
GUYS!
GET OUT OF THE WAY!
HUH?
[ GASPS ]
NO!
MASTER SPLINTER!MASTER SPLINTER!
WHAT JUST HAPPENED?WHERE'S MASTER SPLINTER?
FATHER!
HE JUST -- JUST VANISHED!
THIS CAN'T BE.
MASTER SPLINTER.
WE'RE HOME.
BUT MASTER SPLINTER...
FATHER...
HE'S...
AND IT'S ALL MY FAULT!
[ DOOR CLOSES ]
[ ELECTRICITY CRACKLING ]
[ GRUNTS ]
WHAT? WHERE AM I?
HUH?
THESE ANTIQUATED
PROGRAMMING CODES,
THESE RUDIMENTARY DATA PULSES --
THIS MUST BE
WHAT THE PRIMITIVE HUMANS
ONCE CALLED "THE INTERNET."
WHAT A PATHETIC
AND FEEBLE DISPLAY.
HOW LONG MUST I SEARCH
IN THIS ARCHAIC NETHERWORLD
BEFORE FINDING SOMETHING
WITH ENOUGH POWER
TO REPAIR MY DAMAGES?
HMM.
WHAT IS THIS?
IT APPEARS TO BE
SOME SORT OF DATA VAULT.
WHY, THIS EMANATES
A POWER SOURCE
FAR SUPERIOR TO THIS OTHERWISE
ANCIENT TECHNOLOGY.
I WILL DRAW ITS POWER
INTO MY MATRIX
AND ESCAPE
THIS OUTMODED CYBERSPACE
AND DISPOSE OF THE TURTLES
AS I DID THEIR FEEBLE MASTER.
STRANGE.
I AM UNABLE TO ACCESS IT.
[ GRUNTS ]
THIS RUDIMENTARY PIECE OF TECH
WILL NOT DEFY MY WILL.
WHAT? NO!
AAAAAAH!
YES!
I LIVE!
[ LAUGHS EVILLY ]
--Captions by VITAC--
www.vitac.com
CAPTIONS PAID FOR BY
4KIDS PRODUCTIONS, INC.
IT'S NINJA TIME!IT'S NINJA TIME!
♪ IN THE CITY, ON THE SCENE,
UNDERGROUND, OR IN BETWEEN ♪
♪ THERE'S A MEAN, GREEN TEAM OF
HEROES LIKE YOU'VE NEVER SEEN ♪
♪ AND WHEN THE VILLAINS
AND TURTLES FIGHT ♪
♪ IT'S GONNA BE
ONE SHELL OF A SIGHT ♪
♪ YOU KNOW
THE TURTLES GOT YOUR ♪
♪ BACK, BACK TO THE SEWER
♪ TEENAGE MUTANT NINJA TURTLES
♪
♪ BACK, BACK TO THE SEWER
♪ TEENAGE MUTANT NINJA TURTLES
♪
ROLL CALL!
♪ LEONARDO, DONATELLO
♪ RAFAEL, MICHELANGELO
♪ I LOVE BEING A TURTLE
♪ THERE'S A MEAN, GREEN TEAM OF
HEROES LIKE YOU'VE NEVER SEEN ♪
♪ DOIN' EVERYTHING THEY CAN
♪ TO STOP EVIL SHREDDER'S PLAN
♪
♪ OH, YEAH, THE TURTLES ARE
♪ BACK, BACK TO THE SEWER
♪ TEENAGE MUTANT NINJA TURTLES
♪
♪ BACK, BACK TO THE SEWER
♪ TEENAGE
MUTANT NINJA TURTLES ♪
♪ BACK TO THE SEWER