- ♪
- [grunting]
Ah!
Ha!
- Face it, Teen Blunder,
your days of do-going
are at an end.
- Never, you techno-clad fiend.
The power of my mantle
will always pierce
the darkness of evil.
- ♪
- It is you who will lose
this day, Mechazar.
- I think not.
- Ah!
- Uh!
Awesome!
- It's ninja time!
- ♪ In the city, on the scene,
underground, and in between ♪
♪
♪ There's a mean,
green team of heroes ♪
♪ That you've never seen
♪ And when the villains
and turtles fight ♪
♪ It's gonna be one
shell of a sight ♪
♪ You know the turtles
got your back ♪
♪ Back, back to the Sewer
♪ Teenage Mutant Ninja Turtles
- Roll call!
- ♪ Leonardo, Donatello
♪ Raphael, Michelangelo
- ♪ I love bein' a turtle
- ♪ There's a mean,
green team of heroes ♪
♪ That you've never seen
♪ And they're doin'
everything they can ♪
♪ To stop
evil Shredder's plan ♪
♪ Oh yeah,
the turtles are back ♪
♪ Back, back to the Sewer
♪ Teenage Mutant Ninja Turtles
♪ Back to the Sewer ♪
- ♪
- Thanks for getting me
out of the lab, Mikey.
I've been going crazy all week.
- Well, let's face it, dude.
Donnie and Leo don't need a hand
tracking down
Splinter's last few data bytes.
- Yeah.
And don't get me started
on wedding planning
with Casey and April.
I don't know a boutonniere
from a buccaneer.
I'm an action man.
I'm almost sorry
we took down old Shred head.
- Well, I promised you
adventure.
And thar she blows.
- RAPH: Super villains.
Oh, yeah.
Time to kick some--
- Whoa!
Widen your lens, kick draw.
Those aren't super baddies.
- [indistinct chatter]
- MIKEY: They're super geeks.
- By Gordon's Hammer, one,
please.
- MIKEY: We're
at New York's Comic Caucus.
The premiere superhero,
fantasy, sci-fi,
adventure event of the year.
An event so awesome, even
the Turtle Titan will be there!
- Oh, crud.
- But, wait, there's more.
He's bringing along his new,
ever-allegiant sidekick
Tortoise Boy,
the Shelled Wonder!
That's you, Raph.
Made the booties myself.
- RAPH: And I'll tell you
where you can shove 'em.
- Please have your tickets out.
Form a single-file line.
- Ow!
- Hey!
Ow!
- Let's keep it orderly, people.
Nice and orderly.
- ♪
- Uh!
- At last.
- I'm sorry, but
that's not for sale.
That's a one of a kind, genuine,
superhero cape
in near-mint condition.
- You don't say.
- I certainly do say.
I found it
when I was just a boy.
It just fell out of the sky,
glowing and everything.
And do you know
what I did with it then?
- Try it on?
- What?
And get it all dirty?
No, I had it slabbed, like any
serious comic collector would.
This cape is the jewel
of my collection.
It hasn't been out of
its airtight case in 40 years.
It's my prized possession.
- Yes, I've read your blog.
But, oh well,
if it's not for sale,
I guess
I'll just have to take it!
- Aaah!
Help!
Security!
Ahh!
- [grunts]
- For the last time, Mikey,
I ain't playing
dolly dress-up with you.
- Fine.
Then I guess the Turtle Titan
flies alone.
Uh!
- ♪
- I'm out of here.
- MAN: Stop, thief!
Don't let him get away.
- Hey, Turtle Titan,
what's it like hanging out
with the Justice Force?
- It's nonstop crime fighting.
Want an autograph?
- Uh, some superhero.
- ♪
- That cape does not
belong to you!
For the last time, stop!
Uh!
- [laughing]
- You all right, pal?
- Boy, where am I?
- All this for a stupid cape?
You need to get a life, geek.
- Or perhaps I will simply
take yours.
- Ah!
[grunting]
- You've interfered
with the plans of...
the greatest evil mind
of our time.
Dr. Malignus.
[evil laughing]
- ♪
- Give me that cape,
and I'll let you live.
- Come and get it, doc.
- As you wish.
Ah!
- [gunshots]
- Mmm.
Mm-mm, come to papa.
Eugh!
Ah, come on!
- [gunshots]
- Huh?
- Whoa, Dr. Malignus.
This is a job
for the Turtle Titan!
- Uh!
- [explosion]
- Uh, I see my reputation
precedes me.
- [clears throat]
- Oh.
[laughs] Hi, Justice Force.
- Good to see you again,
Turtle Titan.
Raptarr, get that man
to a hospital.
- Hang tight, old-timer.
- We were making an appearance
at the convention
when we heard the explosions.
It looked like you were holding
your own against Malignus.
Impressive.
- I have my moments.
- Yeah, yeah, big deal.
I've taken on Malignus myself.
Remember when I saved you
from his mind-controlling
nano-bots, SS?
- Sure, I do.
But Malignus
is much more powerful now
than he was back then.
- Clearly your brother
has some moves.
- Mmm.
Of course he does.
- Ah!
[grunting]
- He's Tortoise Boy,
the Turtle Titan's
ever-allegiant sidekick.
I taught him
everything he knows.
- [machine beeping]
- Did you teach him that?
- Huh?
Raph, you get taller?
- ♪
- Clearly, the cape
has transformative powers.
- Tell me something
I don't know.
- That's ten tons
of hydraulic pressure,
and you've barely
broken a sweat.
Raise the pressure
another ten percent, Ananda.
- [siren wailing]
- Go to full power.
- [machine stops]
- ALL: [gasping]
- [cracks neck]
- How much longer do I gotta go
through these tests?
- Long enough for us
to determine the full scope
of the cape's powers.
So far, they seem limitless.
- [grunts]
- But where could something
so powerful have come from?
- That's easy, sonny.
Outerspace.
That's the cape
of the Green Mantle.
- MIKEY: Zippy Lad,
Stainless Steve Steel.
- The green who?
- Not surprised you've never
heard of him, Tsunami.
Old GM was before your time.
But he was one of the greats.
- You bet ya.
- A titan among titans.
A hero among heroes.
And a singular human chosen
by an alien tailor to receive
a rare and special gift--
a super-powered cape.
With this gift, he chose
to become Earth's defender.
Until the day when his arch foe
Mechazar got the better of him.
The Green Mantle fell,
slipping back into obscurity,
never to be heard from again.
But it looks like you've
picked up his mantle, son.
And if you ask me, it suits you.
How 'bout it?
Up for being
the new Green Mantle?
- Uh, umm.
Why not?
- What?
No way.
Give me the cape.
He's no superhero.
- Don't worry, Mikey.
If you want,
you can be my sidekick.
Lame-o Lad.
- What's troubling you, Sentry?
- Malignus.
He's not easily deterred.
He tried for the cape once.
And he'll try again.
- MIKEY: [grunting]
- ♪
- It should be mine.
It will be mine!
And once I have it,
I'll destroy the Justice Force
and rule the world.
But to get it, I'll need
a little help from my friends.
[evil laughing]
- ♪
- This is Channel Six news
reporting that the Justice Force
has just announced
a new member in their ranks.
The new Green Mantle.
- Justice Force, go!
- REPORTER: And off they go
in their never-ending battle
for justice.
- Wait up!
[grunts]
Doh!
Taxi.
- Where to?
- Follow that superhero team.
Ah!
- ♪
- [baby crying]
- The fire is spreading.
- Not on my watch.
- Never fear,
the Turtle Titan is--
Uh!
[grunting]
- [gunshots]
- [tires squealing]
- [laughing]
- ALL: Huh?
- You punks going somewhere?
- Uh!
- Freeze!
- [siren wails]
- Never fear, the Turtle Titan
is--is--
[grunting]
Ah!
- [laughing]
- Mayday! Mayday!
- Huh?
- [horn honks]
- Never fear,
the Turtle Titan is--
- We're saved!
- All right!
- ♪
- What a day.
Hard to believe you just joined
the team this morning, Mantle.
You're an inspiration to us all.
- Hey, just doing my job.
Night now.
- ♪
- Wow, a guy could
get used to this.
- [bell ringing]
- No rest for the righteous.
All right, crud bags,
get ready to--
- [bell stops]
- Okay.
Either I'm dealing with
the fastest thieves ever or--
- Or it's a setup.
You just fell for
the oldest trick in the book.
You'd know that if you knew
anything about superheroes.
- What's your problem,
Lame-o Lad?
- That cape should be mine!
[grunting]
Okay, okay.
How 'bout we share it?
You know, take shifts,
alternate weekends.
I just wanna have superpowers!
- Mm.
Here's the thing, Mikey.
You're just not responsible
enough to have them.
- [grunts]
Aaah!
- Hey!
Cut it out!
I can't see!
Stop!
- [crash]
- [coughing]
- Ah-ha!
Ah-ha!
I'm the new Green Mantle!
- Ah!
Give me that!
- Ow!
Uh, no fair.
I didn't get to fly or anything.
- I'm through playing games
with you.
- Oh, yeah?
Oh, no!
Dr. Malignus!
- Uh, where?
- Ha, ha!
- Mikey, it really is Malignus!
- Really?
- No, not really.
How dumb are you?
- BOTH: [grunting]
- Let go!
It's mine.
Give me.
- [fabric ripping]
- Uh!
- Gotta say,
for a super-powered cape,
it's kind of low quality.
- MALIGNUS: Fools!
- Huh?
- MALIGNUS: Do you realize
what you've done?
The Green Mantle's cape
is only super-powered
when it's being worn.
I spent years
studying its origins,
its secrets, its powers.
And just as long
tracking it down.
And now you ridiculous terrapins
have destroyed it!
- Look, Raph, Malignus.
- And for that,
I will destroy you!
- Yeah?
You and what army?
- Funny you should ask.
- Huh!
- Ah!
- [evil laughing]
- ♪
- Now, be destroyed!
[evil laughing]
- This is all your fault, Raph.
- My fault?
- [gunshots]
- You ripped the cape.
- I ripped it?
You ripped it.
- Loser breath.
- Gopher brain.
- [gunshots]
- [explosions]
- Ah!
- ♪
- Sweet!
It still works!
- ♪
- Well, what do you know?
[laughing]
- Ow!
[grunting]
- That's for calling me
loser breath.
Uh!
Crud!
We each got half the power.
- And your half can't fly.
[laughing]
Na, na, na!
- [explosion]
- I felt that.
- Again, my pets, fire!
- Take us up!
We're sitting ducks down here.
- [explosions]
- Listen, we're not gonna last
very long, bro, if we don't
stop fighting and start working
together on this.
- [explosions]
- BOTH: Uh!
- Time for a team up.
- Enough said.
Let's flatten these wind-ups
once and for all.
- ♪
- Nice!
- BOTH: [grunts]
- Fools!
Did you really think you
would leave here unscathed?
The Mantle's cape makes you
invincible to everything.
Everything except this.
A yellow thimble from the planet
your cape was woven upon.
Harmless to anyone else.
But lethal to a Green Mantle!
So long as you're wearing
his cape,
you're vulnerable
to its effects.
[evil laughing]
- RAPH: Hey, Malignus, catch!
- Ow!
Oh, sometimes I say too much.
- ♪
- Ugh!
- That's what happens
to evildoers
when their paths
cross the Turtle Titan!
- And Tortoise Boy,
the Shelled Wonder.
- [laughing]
- ♪
- You really want to give it up?
I'm sure it can be repaired.
- Thanks, but it's not that.
I ain't really
the superhero type.
- And Turtle Titan
is hero enough for me.
- I'll take it then.
The old girl used to be mine,
after all.
- Gentlemen, meet Al Gordon,
the original Green Mantle.
- The guard
from the convention?
No way!
- Been years since anyone
has called me the Green Mantle.
But once upon a time,
it was true.
- Al contacted me as soon
as he came to at the hospital.
- I'd given up hope
of ever finding this.
Spent 25 years
on the police force,
retired and took on
this security gig.
Protecting the public
is just in my blood.
Turns out,
you don't need superpowers
to fight crime in this world.
- [electricity buzzing]
- ♪
- Of course, they don't hurt
either.
- ALL: [laughing]
- ♪